## VAIBHAV DEKATEY

+917620896333

vaibhav2001dekatey@gmail.com Linkedin Behance Portfolio Website

#### ABOUT ME

Energetic, exceptionally creative and dependable software and frontend developer. Experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming with strong organizational skills, and meticulous attention to detail. I enjoy learning new skills and implementing them in real life!

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Technology, D. Y. Patil International University

2019 - 2023

Computer Science and Engineering

#### **SKILLS**

Technical Skills Other Skills

Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, NodeJs, jQuery, Expressjs, Solidity Graphics Design, Illustration, Framer, Adobe XD, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

#### EXPERIENCE

Feb 2023 - Aug 2023 Intern Remote, Pune.

Wajooba LLC.

- Writing solidity smart contracts.
- Carrying out testing for smart contracts.
- Creating wireframes and prototype of the website.
- Creating front-end for the project.
- Writing documentation.

Intern Jun 2021 - Aug 2021 Remote. Pune

In-house Internship DYPIU

- Automated the lighting system and home appliances using IoT.
- Made an android app based on Blynk libraries to control the appliances.
- Worked with ESP32 Microprocessor along with other components to automate.

#### Co-leader — Outreach & Media Team

Aug 2020 - Mar 2021

Codechef DYPIU

Remote

- In charge of creating new, unique and engaging posts for events.
- In charge social media handles and engaging with the community.
- Lead the Outreach team for DSA 2021

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Open-EXC (DApp Token Exchange)

• Full Fledged Cryptocurrency Exchange built using Hardhat NodeJS etc. on polygon testnet network as a project. Project includes candle stick graphs, realtime token price data and all the features required by a trader in general.

#### T-Portals NFT Project

• An NFT collection generated completely with the help of AI. This is a unique collection as it does not use layer formations like most of the current OpenSea listings.

### Hardware passthrough using KVM.

• Using Arch Linux, Gpu was passed to windows VM on a muxless graphics configuration laptop enabling use of discrete graphics card for the virtual machine.

## Design of Embedded Systems in Home automation

• The project's central aim was to automate daily home appliances using IoT to make our lives simpler and more comfortable.

## Parking Management System

• The project's central aim was to create management system for parking that helps allocate the parking spaces efficiently and to give sense of security to customers parking.

## Jazzy (Discord Music Bot)

• Discord Music Bot that delivers high-quality music to a discord server that can stream music from Youtube and spotify.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking.
- Crash course on python.
- Abstraction, Problem Decomposition, and Functions.
- Blockchain Basics.
- Smart India Hackathon 2022.